-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

X-Chair

Menu

    Shop by Category

    *       [
        
        Save over $500 with all upgrades included](https://www.xchair.com/collections/office-chairs)
    *       [
        
        Featured: X-Tech Ultimate Executive Office Chair](https://www.xchair.com/products/xtech-ultimate-executive-office-chair)

    Shop By Style

    *       [
        
        Explore tables and desks.](https://www.xchair.com/collections/tables-desks)
    *       [
        
        Featured: Standing Desk](https://www.xchair.com/products/standing-desk-rectangle)

    Office Chair Upgrades

    Office Essentials

    *       [
        
        Select upgrades are FREE with office chair purchase.](https://www.xchair.com/collections/accessories)
    *       [
        
        Upgrade with Cooling, Heating and Massaging ELEMAX™](https://www.xchair.com/products/elemax-cooling-heat-and-massage-unit)

    What Makes Us Different

    *       [
        
        Technology And Ergonomics Combined.](https://www.xchair.com/collections/office-chairs)
    *       [
        
        Learn About The Dynamic Variable Lumbar (DVL)® Support.](https://www.xchair.com/pages/ergonomics)

Office Chairs

Shop by Category

Desks & Tables

Shop By Style

Accessories

Office Chair Upgrades

Office Essentials

Why X-Chair

What Makes Us Different

* [0
    
    Shopping Bag](https://www.xchair.com/cart)

Search

Search products 

Your Cart
---------

You are ${ shippingDifference | toUSD } away from free shipping Your cart qualifies for free ground shipping

Subtotal:

[Checkout (${ cartItemCount })](https://www.xchair.com/checkout) Continue Shopping

Your cart is currently empty.

Enable cookies to use the shopping bag

${ cartItemCount }

Privacy Policy
==============

* Effective as of January 1, 2020
* Last Updated April 14, 2022

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Xchair.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

* What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used, and with whom it may be shared.
* What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
* The security procedures in place to protect against the misuse of your information.
* How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside our organization other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

* See what data we have about you if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Email and Text Message Marketing Communications**

When you opt-in for email and/or text message marketing, you can expect to receive weekly communications regarding company information, price changes, promotions, and product announcements.

* You can unsubscribe from email communications at any time. Click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of all X-Chair emails. After this, you will no longer receive marketing email communications from us.
* You can cancel text message communication at any time. Just reply to an X-Chair text sent to you with "STOP" and you will receive a text message to confirm you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive text messages from us.
* If you are experiencing issues with our text messaging, you can reply with "HELP" for more assistance, or you can get help directly at
* Mobile carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.
* Message and data rates may apply for any messages sent to you from us and to us from you.
* This website, Xchair.com, uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart, including when you have abandoned your cart. This information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS and email.

* * *

Cookies Policy
==============

Last updated: October 25, 2022

This Cookies Policy explains what Cookies are and how We use them. You should read this policy so You can understand what type of cookies We use or the information We collect using Cookies and how that information is used.

Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about You may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from Cookies. For further information on how We use, store and keep your personal data secure, see our Privacy Policy.

We do not store sensitive personal information, such as mailing addresses, account passwords, etc. in the Cookies We use.

* * *

Interpretation and Definitions
==============================

Interpretation
--------------

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.

Definitions
-----------

For the purposes of this Cookies Policy:

* **Company** (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Cookies Policy) refers to X-Chair, 8221 Preston Court, Jessup, MD 20794.
* **Cookies** means small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing details of your browsing history on that website among its many uses.
* **Website** refers to X-Chair, accessible from [www.xchair.com](https://www.xchair.com/pages/www.xchair.com)
* **You** means the individual accessing or using the Website, or a company, or any legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Website, as applicable.

* * *

The use of the Cookies
======================

Type of Cookies We Use
----------------------

Cookies can be "Persistent" or "Session" Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close your web browser.

We use both session and persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

* **Necessary / Essential Cookies**
    
    Type: Session Cookies
    
    Administered by: Us
    
    Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.
    
* **Functionality Cookies**
    
    Type: Persistent Cookies
    
    Administered by: Us
    
    Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.
    
* **Tracking and Performance Cookies**
    
    Type: Persistent Cookies
    
    Administered by: Third-Parties
    
    Purpose: These Cookies are used to track information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you use to access the Website. We may also use these Cookies to test new advertisements, pages, features or new functionality of the Website to see how our users react to them.
    
* **Targeting and Advertising Cookies**
    
    Type: Persistent Cookies
    
    Administered by: Third-Parties
    
    Purpose: These Cookies track your browsing habits to enable Us to show advertising more likely to interest You. These Cookies use information about your browsing history to group You with other users who have similar interests. Based on that information, and with Our permission, third-party advertisers can place Cookies to enable them to show adverts which We think will be relevant to your interests while You are on third-party websites.
    
* **Social Media Cookies**
    
    Type: Persistent Cookies
    
    Administered by: Third-Parties
    
    Purpose: In addition to Our own Cookies, We may also use various third parties Cookies to report usage statistics of the Website, deliver advertisements on and through the Website, and so on. These Cookies may be used when You share information using a social media networking website such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter or Google+.

Your Choices Regarding Cookies
------------------------------

If You prefer to avoid using Cookies on the Website, you must first disable the use of Cookies in your browser and then delete the Cookies saved in your browser associated with this website. You may use this option to prevent the use of Cookies at any time.

If You do not accept Our Cookies, You may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Website, and some features may not function properly.

If You'd like to delete Cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse Cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

* For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google: [https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050)
    
* For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft: [http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835](https://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835)
    
* For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla: [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored)
    
* For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple: [https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)

For any other web browser, please visit your web browser's official web pages.

More Information about Cookies
------------------------------

You can learn more about cookies: [What Are Cookies?](https://www.privacypolicies.com/blog/cookies/).

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Cookies Policy, You can contact us:

* By email: service@xchair.com

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information(such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job(for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1- 844-4XCHAIR ([844-492-4247](tel:tel:+1844-492-4247)). International Customers can reach us at: [Service@XChair.com](mailto:Service@xchair.com)**

### SHOP

### SUPPORT

* 

### COMPANY

Copyright © 2024 X-Chair. All Rights Reserved.

[Chat with us](https://www.livechat.com/chat-with/10142132/), powered by [LiveChat](https://www.livechat.com/?welcome)
